const SpeakingData = {
	lesson_number: 1,
	topic: "Describing places",
	lesson_type: "speaking",
	writing_type: "article",
	level: "b1",
	assessment: [],
	topic_content: [
		{
			question: "Describe your favorite place.",
			sample_answer: "My favorite place is the beach.",
			key_words: ["beach", "ocean", "sand"],
		},
		{
			question: "Describe your ideal bedroom.",
			sample_answer:
				"My ideal bedroom would be large and airy, with plenty of natural light. It would have a comfortable bed, a desk for working, and a bookshelf full of books.",
			key_words: ["bedroom", "bed", "desk", "bookshelf"],
		},
		{
			question: "Describe the house in which you grew up.",
			sample_answer:
				"The house in which I grew up was a small, two-story house in the suburbs. It had a big backyard with a swing set and a treehouse. I loved playing in the backyard as a child.",
			key_words: ["house", "backyard", "swing set", "treehouse"],
		},
		{
			question: "Describe what the first house on the moon would look like.",
			sample_answer:
				"The first house on the moon would be a small, self-contained unit. It would have to be able to withstand the harsh conditions of the lunar surface, including extreme temperatures and radiation.",
			key_words: ["house", "moon", "radiation", "temperature"],
		},
		{
			question: "Describe some of your favorite places in your hometown.",
			sample_answer:
				"Some of my favorite places in my hometown are the park, the library, and the museum. I love to go for walks in the park, read books at the library, and learn about history at the museum.",
			key_words: ["park", "library", "museum"],
		},
		{
			question: "Describe a peaceful place that you’ve visited.",
			sample_answer:
				"One peaceful place that I've visited is the Grand Canyon. It's so vast and beautiful, and it's easy to feel at peace there.",
			key_words: ["Grand Canyon", "vast", "beautiful", "peace"],
		},
		{
			question: "Describe a place that exists only in your imagination.",
			sample_answer:
				"A place that exists only in my imagination is a floating island in the sky. It's a beautiful place with lush vegetation and crystal-clear waters.",
			key_words: ["floating island", "sky", "lush vegetation", "crystal-clear waters"],
		},
		{
			question: "Describe a friend’s or family member’s house where you enjoy spending time.",
			sample_answer:
				"One friend's house where I enjoy spending time is my best friend's house. It's always warm and inviting, and her family is always so welcoming.",
			key_words: ["house", "warm", "inviting", "welcoming"],
		},
		{
			question: "Describe your perfect fantasy vacation destination.",
			sample_answer:
				"My perfect fantasy vacation destination is a tropical island with white-sand beaches and crystal-clear waters. I would spend my days swimming, sunbathing, and exploring the island.",
			key_words: ["tropical island", "white-sand beaches", "crystal-clear waters"],
		},
		{
			question: "Describe your favorite store.",
			sample_answer:
				"My favorite store is a bookstore. I love the smell of books and the feeling of browsing the shelves. I can always find something interesting to read at a bookstore.",
			key_words: ["bookstore", "books", "reading"],
		},
	],
}

const SpeakingData2 = {
	lesson_number: 2,
	topic: "Describing family",
	lesson_type: "speaking",
	writing_type: "article",
	level: "b1",
	assessment: [],
	topic_content: [
		{
			question: "Describe your family.",
			sample_answer:
				"I have a large family. I have two parents, two brothers, and one sister. We are all very close and we love spending time together.",
			key_words: ["family", "parents", "brothers", "sister"],
		},
		{
			question: "Describe your parents.",
			sample_answer:
				"My parents are both very kind and loving. They have always been there for me and I am so grateful for them.",
			key_words: ["parents", "kind", "loving"],
		},
		{
			question: "Describe your siblings.",
			sample_answer:
				"My siblings are all very different from each other, but we are all very close. We love to play games together and we always have each other's backs.",
			key_words: ["siblings", "different", "close"],
		},
		{
			question: "Describe your grandparents.",
			sample_answer:
				"I love my grandparents. They are always so happy to see me and they always have the best stories to tell.",
			key_words: ["grandparents", "happy", "stories"],
		},
		{
			question: "Describe your favorite family memory.",
			sample_answer:
				"My favorite family memory is when we went on vacation to the beach. We spent the week swimming, playing in the sand, and building sandcastles. It was so much fun and I will never forget it.",
			key_words: ["vacation", "beach", "swimming", "playing"],
		},
		{
			question: "Describe what your family means to you.",
			sample_answer:
				"My family means the world to me. They are my support system and they always have my back. I am so grateful for them and I love them very much.",
			key_words: ["family", "support system", "love"],
		},
		{
			question: "Describe what you would like to do with your family in the future.",
			sample_answer:
				"I would like to travel the world with my family. I would love to show them all the amazing places that I have been and I would love to make new memories with them.",
			key_words: ["travel", "world", "memories"],
		},
		{
			question: "Describe what you are grateful for about your family.",
			sample_answer:
				"I am grateful for my family for always being there for me. They have always supported me and they have always loved me unconditionally. I am so lucky to have them in my life.",
			key_words: ["family", "support", "love"],
		},
	],
}

const SpeakingData3 = {
	lesson_number: 3,
	topic: "Traveling",
	lesson_type: "speaking",
	writing_type: "article",
	level: "b1",
	assessment: [],

	topic_content: [
		{
			question: "What is your favorite travel destination?",
			sample_answer:
				"My favorite travel destination is Paris. The city has such a charming atmosphere, and there are so many iconic landmarks to visit like the Eiffel Tower and the Louvre.",
			key_words: ["favorite", "travel destination", "Paris", "romantic", "Eiffel Tower", "Louvre"],
		},
		{
			question: "Describe your most memorable travel experience.",
			sample_answer:
				"My most memorable travel experience was when I hiked to the top of Machu Picchu in Peru. The breathtaking views and the sense of accomplishment I felt were truly unforgettable.",
			key_words: ["memorable", "travel experience", "hiked", "Machu Picchu", "Peru", "views", "accomplishment"],
		},
		{
			question: "What is your dream travel destination?",
			sample_answer:
				"My dream travel destination is the Maldives. I would love to relax on the pristine white sand beaches, swim in crystal-clear turquoise waters, and experience the luxury and tranquility of the overwater bungalows.",
			key_words: ["dream", "travel destination", "Maldives", "beaches", "waters", "overwater bungalows"],
		},
		{
			question: "Describe your favorite mode of transportation while traveling.",
			sample_answer:
				"My favorite mode of transportation while traveling is by train. I love the scenic routes, the opportunity to meet fellow travelers, and the comfort and convenience it offers.",
			key_words: [
				"favorite",
				"mode of transportation",
				"train",
				"scenic routes",
				"fellow travelers",
				"comfort",
				"convenience",
			],
		},
		{
			question: "What is your most adventurous travel experience?",
			sample_answer:
				"My most adventurous travel experience was when I went skydiving in New Zealand. The adrenaline rush and the feeling of soaring through the sky was absolutely exhilarating.",
			key_words: ["adventurous", "travel experience", "skydiving", "New Zealand", "adrenaline rush", "soaring"],
		},
		{
			question: "Describe your favorite local cuisine you've tried while traveling.",
			sample_answer:
				"My favorite local cuisine I've tried while traveling is sushi in Japan. The freshness of the ingredients and the skillful artistry in its preparation make it a truly delightful culinary experience.",
			key_words: ["favorite", "local cuisine", "sushi", "Japan", "freshness", "artistry", "culinary experience"],
		},
		{
			question: "What is your preferred travel accommodation?",
			sample_answer:
				"My preferred travel accommodation is staying in boutique hotels. I enjoy the unique charm, personalized service, and attention to detail that boutique hotels offer.",
			key_words: [
				"preferred",
				"travel accommodation",
				"boutique hotels",
				"unique charm",
				"personalized service",
				"attention to detail",
			],
		},
		{
			question: "Describe your favorite travel souvenir or memento.",
			sample_answer:
				"My favorite travel souvenir is a handcrafted necklace I bought from a local artisan in Bali. It not only reminds me of the beautiful beaches and vibrant culture of Bali but also supports the local community.",
			key_words: [
				"favorite",
				"travel souvenir",
				"memento",
				"handcrafted necklace",
				"local artisan",
				"Bali",
				"beaches",
				"vibrant culture",
				"supports local community",
			],
		},
	],
}

const SpeakingData4 = {
	lesson_number: 4,
	topic: "Restaurant",
	lesson_type: "speaking",
	writing_type: "article",
	level: "b1",
	assessment: [],

	topic_content: [
		{
			question: "Describe your favorite type of cuisine.",
			sample_answer:
				"My favorite type of cuisine is Italian. I love the rich flavors of pasta, pizza, and traditional Italian dishes. The use of fresh ingredients and aromatic herbs make Italian cuisine incredibly delicious.",
			key_words: [
				"favorite",
				"type of cuisine",
				"Italian",
				"pasta",
				"pizza",
				"flavors",
				"fresh ingredients",
				"aromatic herbs",
			],
		},
		{
			question: "Describe your most memorable dining experience at a restaurant.",
			sample_answer:
				"My most memorable dining experience at a restaurant was when I celebrated my birthday at a fine dining establishment. The exquisite presentation of each dish, the impeccable service, and the luxurious ambiance made it a truly special and unforgettable occasion.",
			key_words: [
				"memorable",
				"dining experience",
				"restaurant",
				"birthday",
				"fine dining",
				"presentation",
				"service",
				"ambiance",
			],
		},
		{
			question: "What is your favorite restaurant dish?",
			sample_answer:
				"My favorite restaurant dish is a perfectly cooked medium-rare steak with a side of garlic mashed potatoes and roasted vegetables. The juicy and tender steak paired with the creamy potatoes and flavorful vegetables is a culinary delight.",
			key_words: [
				"favorite",
				"restaurant dish",
				"steak",
				"medium-rare",
				"garlic mashed potatoes",
				"roasted vegetables",
				"juicy",
				"tender",
				"flavorful",
			],
		},
		{
			question: "Describe your preferred dining atmosphere in a restaurant.",
			sample_answer:
				"My preferred dining atmosphere in a restaurant is cozy and intimate. I enjoy soft lighting, comfortable seating, and a relaxed ambiance that allows for meaningful conversations and a pleasant dining experience.",
			key_words: [
				"preferred",
				"dining atmosphere",
				"restaurant",
				"cozy",
				"intimate",
				"soft lighting",
				"comfortable seating",
				"relaxed",
				"meaningful conversations",
			],
		},
		{
			question: "What is your most adventurous food experience at a restaurant?",
			sample_answer:
				"My most adventurous food experience at a restaurant was when I tried exotic dishes from a fusion restaurant. From sushi burritos to kimchi tacos, the bold combinations of flavors and cultural influences took my taste buds on a thrilling journey.",
			key_words: [
				"adventurous",
				"food experience",
				"restaurant",
				"exotic dishes",
				"fusion restaurant",
				"sushi burritos",
				"kimchi tacos",
				"flavors",
				"cultural influences",
			],
		},
		{
			question: "Describe your favorite dessert from a restaurant.",
			sample_answer:
				"My favorite dessert from a restaurant is a decadent chocolate lava cake with a scoop of vanilla ice cream. The warm, gooey center of the cake combined with the cool and creamy ice cream creates a delightful contrast of textures and flavors.",
			key_words: [
				"favorite",
				"dessert",
				"restaurant",
				"chocolate lava cake",
				"vanilla ice cream",
				"warm",
				"gooey",
				"cool",
				"creamy",
				"textures",
				"flavors",
			],
		},
		{
			question: "What is your preferred restaurant seating arrangement?",
			sample_answer:
				"My preferred restaurant seating arrangement is a booth or a corner table. I enjoy the privacy and comfort it offers, allowing me to have an intimate dining experience with my companions.",
			key_words: [
				"preferred",
				"restaurant seating arrangement",
				"booth",
				"corner table",
				"privacy",
				"comfort",
				"intimate",
				"dining experience",
				"companions",
			],
		},
		{
			question: "Describe your ideal restaurant for a romantic date night.",
			sample_answer:
				"My ideal restaurant for a romantic date night would be a cozy French bistro with candlelit tables, soft music, and a menu featuring exquisite dishes and fine wines. The intimate setting and romantic ambiance would create a memorable evening for me and my partner.",
			key_words: [
				"ideal",
				"restaurant",
				"romantic date night",
				"cozy French bistro",
				"candlelit tables",
				"soft music",
				"exquisite dishes",
				"fine wines",
				"intimate setting",
				"romantic ambiance",
				"memorable evening",
				"partner",
			],
		},
	],
}

export { SpeakingData, SpeakingData2, SpeakingData3, SpeakingData4 }
